indumenti.se 2014-11-21

# Security and Privacy Policy | Swedish Mens Shirts and Suits At indumenti

Indumenti is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. This statement outlines our privacy and data protection policy.

## COLLECTION AND USE OF USER DETAILS

Personal details of users of Indumenti, such as name and address and email address, will be collected and processed upon registration to our website. The personal information collected on our site is collected and stored in the European Union.

This information is collected for the following purposes:

  * To enable us to handle/fulfill your orders
  * To notify customers of relevant new products or services
  * To notify users of other promotional activities within Indumenti

User information is retained for in-house research to:

  * Improve our understanding of our customers needs in relation to product development, ensure effective communication and aid strategic development.
  * All results of such research and analysis will be collated as aggregated information and will not reveal any personal facts about individual customers.
  * For certain services, such as purchases, we may request credit card or other payment information which we process in encrypted form on secure servers.
  * Indumenti will maintain appropriate measures to ensure that users' personal details are not misused, accidentally destroyed, lost or altered within the Indumenti server environment.

## INFORMATION SHARING

We do not rent or sell your personal information to other companies or individuals. We only provide such information to trusted suppliers for the sole purpose of processing personal information on our behalf, for example our catalogue mailing company. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

## INFORMATION SECURITY

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We restrict access to your personal information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

## UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personal information.

## TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA OVERSEAS

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using it to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing the Indumenti website and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.

## Analytics Tracking

Google Site Stats is now implemented at Indumenti.se to measure the effectiveness of our web campaigns. Please contact our privacy depart for further information.

�

## CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Please note this Security and Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice.

For further information regarding privacy issues please write to:

**Privacy Department**  
Indumenti  
Email: [customerservice@indumenti.se](mailto:customerservice@indumenti.se)
